ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Marical, Margarita [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- San Francisco Joint Board: Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Abby, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- American Cover Company, 1960-1961 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- American Labor ORT, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Ardee Sportswear, Incorporated, 1971-1973 (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Auditors Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Brass, Louis: General Auditor, 1967-1972 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Organization Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Bay Area ILGWU Employers Health and Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Bouquet Fashions, 1973-1975 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Building Corporation, 1947-1973 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Building Corporation: Maple Street Building, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- California Expediters, Incorporated, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- California Youngsters, Incorporated, 1963-1968 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Campaign Contributions, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Campaign Election Reporting Act, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- Campus Modes, Incorporated, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Cannady Creations Sportswear, 1964-1966 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Catalina, Incorporated, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Catalina, Incorporated, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- Catalina, Incorporated: House Calls Reports, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Catalina, Incorporated: House Call Reports, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Catalina, Incorporated: House Call Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1967 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Catalina, Incorporated: House Call Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1967 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Catalina, Incorporated, 1956-1967 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Census Reports, 1963-1975 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Chaikin, Sol C: President, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Chaikin, Sol C: President, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Chana Baker of California, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Boycott of Character Foundations, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Chiara Manufacturing Company, 1967-1969 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Chic Parisienne, 1963-1968 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Chic Lingerie: Redondo Beach, 1962-1966 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- City of Hope, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- Co-Ed Garment Company: Festus, Missouri, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Colton Sportswear Manufacturing Company, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- San Francisco Joint Board: Contracts, 1973-1975 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Charles Cooper, Incorporated, 1963-1969 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Garment Workers Federal Credit Union, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- D'Andre, 1973-1976 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Daniels, Wilbur, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Daniels, Wilbur, 1968-1973 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Daniels, Wilbur: Executive Vice President, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Donations, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Dubinsky, David: Special Assistance Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 24)
- Dubrow, Evelyn, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 25)
- Dubrow, Evelyn: Political Department, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Dumaz and Canez, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 27)
- El Jo Styles, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 28)
- Feinberg, Basil: Esquire, 1970-1977 (Box 95, Folder 29)
- Feinberg, Basil, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 30)
- Financial Reports: Western States Region Administrative Fund, San Fransicso Joint Board, Los Angeles Joint Board, Subordinate Accounts, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 31)
- Financial Reports: Employers Vacation Health and Welfare Fund, 1974-1977 (Box 95, Folder 32)
- Imports, 1973-1977 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Imports, 1973-1977 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Industrial Homework, 1974-1975 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Industrial Welfare, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Justice: Deadline, 1970-1972 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- King County Medical Blue Shield, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Political Legislation, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Political, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Political Legislation, 1975-1976 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Organizers School, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Politics, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Political Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Mode O'Day: Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Coats and Suits: Negotiations, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Histadrut, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Illegal Aliens, 1974-1976 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Anjac Fashions: Negotiations, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association: Negotiations, 1976-1977 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Label Distribution and Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- Landag Manufacturing Company, 1973-1976 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Leone, Carlo: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, 1969-1972 (Box 96, Folder 22)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 23)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, Director Central Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 96, Folder 24)
- Leviton, Philip, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 25)
- Lipsig, James: Assistant Executive Secretary, 1974-1976 (Box 96, Folder 26)
- Local 270, 1972-1974 (Box 96, Folder 27)
- Local 271, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 28)
- Local 293, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 29)
- Local 399, 1969-1972 (Box 96, Folder 30)
- Local 451, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 31)
- Local 497, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 32)
- Local 293: Investigations, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 33)
- Lokiec, Mitchell: Director Management Engineering Department, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 34)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturing Association, 1973-1976 (Box 96, Folder 35)
- Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO, 1975-1977 (Box 96, Folder 36)
- Los Angeles Independent Manufacturers and Jobbers, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 37)
- ILGWU, Los Angeles Joint Board: Merger, 1965-1974 (Box 96, Folder 38)
- Loubella Extendables, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 39)
- Margolis, Bernard, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 40)
- ILGWU: Memo/For Staff Only, 1976-1977 (Box 96, Folder 41)
- Memorandum, 1975-1977 (Box 96, Folder 42)
- Wan, William F.T., 1969-1974 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Western States Region: Seminar, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Western States Region: Seminar, Conference, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Western Union, 1974-1977 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Zimny, Max: General Counsel, 1974-1977 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Zimny, Max: General Counsel, 1972-1974 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Wall, Cornelius: Letters of Members, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Wall, Cornelius, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Wall, Cornelius: Personal, 1944-1974 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Retiree Service Department, 1966-1972 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Fred Rothschild of California: Negotiations, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Fred Rothschild of California, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Fred Rothschild of California, 1975-1976 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Fred Rothschild of California [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1977 (Box 97, Folder 15)
- Fred Rothschild of California [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1977 (Box 97, Folder 16)
- United States Senate and Congress Letters: HR 2410 and 520, 1975-1977 (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Rolnick, Louis: ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 18)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company, 1974-1977 (Box 97, Folder 19)
- Strike Sanction Requests, 1975-1976 (Box 97, Folder 20)
- Strike Sanction Requests, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Stulberg, Louis: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 22)
- Stulberg, Louis: Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 97, Folder 23)
- Stulberg, Louis: Elections, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 24)
- Style Art, 1974-1976 (Box 97, Folder 25)
- Rolnick, Louis: Supplementary Unemployment Benefit Fund, 1975-1977 (Box 97, Folder 26)
- Western Union Telegram, 1961-1974 (Box 97, Folder 27)
- Texfi Industries, Incorporated: Company Leaflets and Letters, 1972-1974 (Box 97, Folder 28)
- Texfi West, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 29)
- Texfi Industries, Incorporated: Legal, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 30)
- Tyler, Gus: Assistant President, 1973-1977 (Box 97, Folder 31)
- Tyler, Gus: Assistant President, 1969-1972 (Box 97, Folder 32)
- United Farm Workers, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 33)
- Wall, Cornelius, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 34)
- Wall, Cornelius: Letters of Members, 1976-1977 (Box 97, Folder 35)